Ashish Tewari (1) Featured

Member of Technical Staff seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ReactJS, AngularJS, NodeJS, Spring Boot, Spring Cloud.AWS.Java.Microservices



Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Noida Notice Period: 15 Days or less Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. Maintenance [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Member of Technical Staff, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ReactJS, Angular JS, NodeJS, Spring

Boot, Spring Cloud, AWS, Java, Microservices

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Result oriented professional with 6.7 years of experience in Development and Maintenance of Oracle Order & Service Management. Application Development, Application Maintenance, Application Support, Design Architecture, Requirement Gathering, Requirement Analysis, Order Management, Service Management, Client Management, Defect Management, C, C++, JAVA, C#, Visual BASIC

Work Experience

Oracle India Private Limited as Member Technical Staff -Java Jul 2013 to Jun 2018

Oracle Communication Solutions Integrations (CSI)

July 2014 - June 2018 | Hyderabad

Working in cloud solutions, providing end to end solution for Communications Business from order capture to fulfillment. Technologies used are J2EE, Sprint Boot, Spring Cloud, Hibernate, EclipseLink, Docker, Linux programming, NodeJs, AngularJS, ReactJS, ReactNative, Kafka, Microservices architecture.

Worked with Oracle Communication Solutions Integrations (CSI) Team in the capacity of a developer to integrate edge applications such as OSM, Siebel CRM, BRM and their counterparts on the cloud. We use SOA suite and AIA Communications PIPS for performing the integration.

Oracle Order and Service Management (OSM)

July 2013 - June 2014 | Hyderabad

Development and Maintenance of Oracle Order & Service Management.

Applied knowledge in structuring different code units using Industry standard patterns and algorithms.

Technologies used and concepts harnessed include - OOPS, Design Pattern, Data Structures, J2EE, Python, Oracle Application Development Framework (ADF), Design Architecture, Oracle Weblogic Server, Oracle Database, SOAP.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from IIT Roorkee, Roorkee, Uttarakhand in 2013

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
C, C++, JAVA, C#, Visual basic		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Perl, Python, PHP, Bash, Ruby		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
HTML, XML		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
SQL, Xquery		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
XSLT, SOAP, Web Services		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Oracle SOA Suite, Spring		6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
J2EE	0	6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Hibernate	0	6 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
DOCKER	0	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Linux	0	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time